[theme music playing]
- [Young-man pants]
- [Gye-young] Oh, come on, hurry up.
[Soo-jeong] Oh, it's coming.
- [chuckles]
- [Gye-young] Man...
- Can't that thing take me home?
- [Kyung-sik] This is Opera. Fish, respond.
- They do that?
- [Gye-young] Should I ask?
- This is Opera. Fish, respond.
- [Soo-jeong] Can't hurt to ask.
Are helicopters supposed to
shake like that?
- [Kyung-sik] Fish respond.
- I've never seen one this close,
but it does seem like
it's shaking quite a bit.
[Kyung-sik] Opera. Fish respond.
Maybe it's just turbulence
from the wind or something.
[Kyung-sik] This is Opera, Opera.
Fish, respond.
[radio static whooshing]
[Kyung-sik] This is Opera, Opera.
Fish, respond.
- [Tae-hwa] Hwang Kyung-sik!
- [Kyung-sik] Private Hwang Kyung-sik!
- You reach them yet?
- They won't respond.
[Tae-hwa]
They seem like bad pilots. Be careful.
[Kyung-sik] Yes, sir.
- [In-ho] Hey!
- [Gye-young] No, stay here.
Wait, wait.
- Sir!
- [Soo-jeong] Wait, hey!
Hey, Ra In-ho!
What is that brat doing?
You can't be here.
Get your head out of your ass!
- You little shit.
- [grunts]
Sir, you can't let them land.
Look what I saw.
[Tae-hwa sighs]
Shit.
[Gye-young] Huh?
[all exclaim]
- [radio beeps]
- [Kyung-sik] This is Opera.
- Fish respond.
- [radio static whooshing]
[Tae-hwa panting]
- For God's sake. Walk normally.
- [Young-joo moaning]
Hold on, hold on. Wait.
Okay, come on. Let's go in there.
Go inside. Quick, quick.
- Quick, quick.
- [continues moaning]
Oh, shit!
- Shit! Stop following me, okay?
- Hey, open up!
Find your own place. [chuckles]
[wags tongue mockingly]
[Tripeater grunts]
[softly] Oh, shit.
[shudders nervously]
[hesitates]
- N... Nobody?
- [Young-joo] I'm not even drunk.
- [Jin-wook] My head hurts.
- [Tripeater] I'm sober.
- [Young-joo laughs] Exactly.
- [Tripeater] We're heavyweights.
- Yeah.
- [Young-joo sighs]
- We should...
- I'm tired.
- [Young-joo] Let's have a drink!
- Yeah! Cheers, Boozer!
- They are insane.
- [Tripeater] To not being zombies.
[people screaming]
- [Young-joo] What's going on?
- [Tae-shik] Fire in the hole!
[Tripeater] Wait, that's a zombie.
- [Jin-wook exclaims]
- Whoa!
- Fire in the hole.
- [Tripeater] See that?
- Oh, it's Alex.
- That was sick.
- He's there. It's Alex.
- Alex.
Alex, look over here, over here.
[Young-joo gasps]
- [tires screech]
- Ah, shit!
[Alex shuddering]
[both cheering]
- Good game!
- That was crazy to watch.
- That was so cool.
- Cheers to that!
- [Tripeater] Encore, encore.
- Are you guys serious?
All right. I think that
you've had enough. Here.
Drink this.
[sniffs] Nasty!
- Jesus Christ.
- [Tae-shik] Hurry.
- [Young-joo] Give my beer back.
- [Tae-shik] Open the door.
- [Tripeater] Alex.
- I always do the dirty work.
- [Young-joo] Let him in.
- Right away, sir.
- [Young-joo] That was awesome.
- [Tripeater] He's dope.
- Come on, come on.
- [Tae-shik panting]
- [Tripeater] Bravo! Wow!
- [Young-joo] Alex!
[Tripeater] Ah, I think I got too wasted.
You're so cool. Encore. Do an encore. Oh!
- A zombie.
- [Young-joo] Oh!
[Tripeater] Go, go!
Now they're all fighting each other.
Yeah, go Twins!
- [cheers]
- Hey, root for the Giants not the Twins.
The Twins.
- Let's go, Giants! Bang!
- Twins, let's go.
[Tae-shik singing] ♪ Fi-ga-ro ♪
[Tripeater] Go Giants!
[helicopter blades whirring]
[Tae-hwa panting]
Ready your stations.
Prepare small arms and anti-aircraft fire.
All gunners to your stations, now!
[Jae-yoon gasps]
[Young-man gasps]
[Jae-yoon] What?
Stations, now!
[thrilling music playing]
This way!
[zombies snarling]
Gunner, be ready to neutralize
once it's in range.
Ready to neutralize when in range!
- [whirring]
- [Tae-hwa panting]
They're still too far away!
Ready your weapons.
Aim and fire! Shoot it in the tail.
- Ah, shit.
- Get it right if you wanna go home.
Do you boys want to die today?
Shit. Neutralize that target!
- [Young-man] Neutralizing target!
- Neutralizing target!
[In-ho] Neutralizing target!
[Tae-hwa] Aim for the tail.
Tail. Yes, sir.
Aim for the tail!
- Where's the target?
- It's almost in range.
[Young-man breathing shakily]
- Neutralize the target!
- Beam discharge!
One, two...
- Firing rounds! [grunts]
- [shots firing]
Bring it down!
[helicopter blades whirring]
[sighs in relief]
[Young-joo groans]
Feel like I'm gonna die.
Whoa!
Look up there.
- [Young-joo groans]
- We need to keep moving.
Come on, go.
They're gone.
- Come on.
- Right.
- Keep Young-joo close.
- Come here.
- [sighs] Careful.
- [Young-joo] I feel like death.
- [Tae-shik] Keep your eyes open.
- [Jin-wook] You're okay. Hang in there.
- [Tripeater] It's clear.
- [Tae-shik] Okay.
[Tripeater] Let's go.
Why the hell does the price of
a helicopter matter right now?
[Commander on phone]
How dare you shout at me?
What's your problem?
Are you out of your mind?
Sir. I'm sorry.
At this point,
since no more supplies will be sent,
it could serve us to move to
the base camp in Suseo, at least for now.
We'll run out of food
and water if we stay.
We only have a few days.
So if there's any way that we could join
the base camp setup in Suseo--
Stay there and stop talking nonsense.
I need you to lead. Can I count on you?
Yeah.
I'll check on the situation
and get back to you. Understand?
Yeah. Copy that.
Salute. [sighs]
[grunts angrily]
Piece 'a shit!
You want us to stay in this hellhole
and get ourselves killed?
Motherfucker, I swear to God.
All of you, focus.
I've spoken to the commander.
We're leaving this building today.
[all exclaim in surprise]
Is that order... because of the resupply?
The resupply... [sighs]
There isn't one.
We can hold out, sir.
We can make it a few weeks without food.
- Ah!
- Young-man's right.
We have the hotel water supply.
The hotel's water tank
has more than enough water.
However, the electricity
will go out shortly,
and the pump supplying the water
from the tank won't work without it,
No, but, sir. Why don't we just go
when the electricity cuts out?
- Right, sir?
- [Jae-yoon clearing throat]
You're gonna pick up a gun
while barely surviving on water?
Ah, shit.
It would behoove us to get moving now,
while we still have our strength.
At this point,
the only option we have left,
- is to fight our way out of here.
- [In-ho] Hmm.
[Tae-hwa sighs]
What is it?
I want...
I want a weapon, too.
[Tae-hwa sighs]
All right, listen here.
I know everything that's happened here
is far from normal.
Just don't push it.
You already saw
what I can do with a gun. I--
I was a shooting athlete
all through high school.
I made it to
the National Reserve team, sir.
I am more confident as a rifleman...
than any of your men.
If you want me to take a test...
then I will, but...
[breathing shakily]
I need to defend myself, sir.
- [Tae-shik] Wow.
- [Tripeater] Wow.
- [Jin-wook] Holy shit!
- [Tripeater] Shit.
- [Jin-wook] What the fuck happened?
- [Tae-shik] What a mess!
[Jin-wook] Is this Gangnam station?
This isn't how I thought I'd look.
This place got destroyed.
[Jin-wook] Well, fuck me.
What a warm welcome.
[zombies snarling]
Well, at least the ambulance arrived.
You said there's soldiers in there?
[Young-joo sobbing]
Jae-yoon's in there. [crying]
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Hey!
You really wanna do that?
You don't see zombies in there.
Those things will rip you apart.
[snarling continues]
I agree with Jin-wook.
If we go in there, we're all dead.
Let's wait till Jae-yoon calls.
We'll find shelter somewhere.
- Okay?
- I'm sure he'll call soon.
Let's just go to the parking lot.
Yeah. You should try
not to worry about it.
Let's get outta here.
[Jin-wook sighs]
- [Young-joo sobs]
- Let's go. You can't go in there.
[Tripeater] Yeah. So hurry up, Boozer.
Come with us. Come on.
[Tae-shik] They really took it over, huh?
[Young-joo] Jae-yoon.
[Tae-shik] It's like a zombie expo.
Oh, great. Looks like
they made their way down here.
- [Tripeater] Did they throw a rager here?
- [Jin-wook] It's swarming with 'em.
[Tae-shik] Is there anything in the car?
God, there's blood all over.
- [Tripeater] Maybe it runs?
- [Tae-shik] Don't go on your own.
[frightening music playing]
Hold on. Hold on.
Wait. The plate's 4574.
We'll look in teams of two, all right?
- Are you sure that it's in this area?
- That's why we're here.
Navy blue Hummer. You got that?
Wait a second.
You really don't remember
where you parked your car?
[Tae-shik] No, the valet parks for me...
Hey, um... Sorry that I got so mad.
It's your fault, honestly.
If I let you run in there with that,
you'd already be dead right now.
- Does that make sense?
- [Tripeater] What's that? Guys!
- Run!
- Young-joo, run!
- Come on.
- Run!
- [zombies snarling]
- [both screaming]
[snarls]
[Young-joo shouting]
Get away! No!
[shouting]
[Tae-shik] Fire in the hole!
Fire in the hole!
[Jin-wook] Get out!
- Fire in the hole!
- Young-joo!
[Tae-shik] Get outta there!
[Tae-shik] ...in the hole!
Fire in the hole!
[yelling]
[screaming]
[squelching]
- Alex, no!
- Are you trying to get yourself killed?
What are you doing? No, Seo Jin-wook!
- [yelling]
- Get in!
- Fuck! Listen to me. Get in there.
- No!
[Young-joo crying]
[Tripeater crying]
- [Young-joo] Alex.
- Fuck off!
- [glass breaking]
- [Tripeater] Alex. Alex.
[Young-joo crying]
[Tripeater crying] Alex.
Hey, no. I'm coming.
[wailing]
Alex!
[crying hysterically]
No! No!
[Tripeater crying]
Listen, I know you're all scared.
But we still need to win, regardless.
Why, Hwang Kyung-sik?
Private Hwang Kyung-sik!
Sir, it's because we're soldiers of Korea.
[chuckles] Not quite.
You'd give the president that answer.
Oh.
Sir, I'm sorry.
Do you know what winning truly is?
Its surviving.
Survivors are the real winners.
Do you know the quote by Yi Sun-shin?
Anyone here?
"Those who are willing to die will not.
Those aiming only to live will die."
Correct.
We're gonna do this with all we've got,
and make it back home.
[all] All that we've got!
[Tae-hwa] Okay.
Now, all of you, get ready.
[sniffles, cries]
[Tae-hwa] We'll move to
the hotel VIP lounge through the stairs,
and take the elevator the rest of the way.
Got it? Let's go.
[panting] Kim Young-man,
Kwak Gye-young, open it.
- Yes sir, right away.
- Right away!
Don't shoot until I say so,
am I understood?
[all] Holding fire.
- Now switch to short burst.
- [all] Switch to short burst.
I'll count to three. One...
Two...
Three.
[thrilling music playing]
- [In-ho whimpers]
- [Jae-yoon] God. What--
[Soo-jeong] Oh, that's foul.
What the hell is that?
- [all overlapping, exclaiming]
- [In-ho] What the hell?
[zombie snarling]
- [all yelling]
- [Tae-hwa] Open fire!
[all yelling, overlapping]
- [Soo-jeong] Oh, my gosh.
- [In-ho] Shoot it!
[Jae-yoon] Oh, look out!
It's still moving. Holy, shit.
[In-ho] Shoot it!
[pensive music playing]
[Tripeater sobbing]
[sniffles]
[sobbing]
Hey!
Looks like the car isn't here,
so you should go
and search somewhere else!
[Tripeater scoffs]
What?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- [Young-joo shouts]
[scoffs] You coward.
Are you insane, asshole?
I'm gonna come out
and rip your face off.
I'll throw you all the fucking way
across the parking garage.
Oh, no... What should I do?
You're lucky that I--
Just go over there,
go and get the stupid car
and drive it back, okay?
But I never learned how.
So you don't even have
your license, or anything?
- I failed the test, so no!
- [Jin-wook scoffs]
- I'll leave if you act like this.
- Hey, hold on. Just wait.
[grunts frustratedly]
Wait, hey! We'll use our phones.
I think mine still has battery.
What's your number?
- [Tripeater] Hmm?
- [Young-joo] Your number.
[Gye-young screaming]
- [In-ho] Do you see any more?
- [Young-man] Go!
[Tae-hwa] Be careful. Move.
[Young-man] You sure they're dead?
[In-ho whimpers]
[Jae-yoon coughing]
[Young-man] Hurry up, move, move!
[all panting]
[grunts]
[all exclaim in disbelief]
[gnarly music playing]
Look at this shit.
What's the price of a helicopter
when all this is going on?
They want us to pay
for the one you shot down.
- [all gasping]
- Ah... The supply one?
And you're all accomplices
so we'll split the bill later.
[In-ho gasps]
- Me too? But--
- How much is a helicopter?
- I think expensive, sir.
- Shit. We're screwed.
- Me too?
- Shit.
- Um...
- I was kidding.
[In-ho chuckles]
- [Tae-hwa sighs]
- [In-ho laughs nervously]
Before we all head downstairs,
we'll go into pairs
and begin with the lounge.
If everything's clear,
then we'll all maintain our guns,
which will determine if we win today.
Then we'll move ahead to
the next location and secure it.
Do you all understand? Are you ready?
[all] Yes, we are.
Very good. Let's move
and begin the search.
[all] Yes, sir.
Come on, let's go.
[zombies snarling]
How am I gonna find this thing?
This... Ah... Ah...
- [car alarm beeps]
- Oh, my God.
Hell, yeah. There we go. That's it.
What's... 45... 74...
Ha!
Oh, man.
Sorry, Zombies. Can you guys move?
Excuse me, sorry.
Go. There's nobody for you to eat.
[zombies snarling]
God, I don't know how to work this thing.
BOOZER
[ringtone beeping]
- Hello?
- All right. You in the car?
- Yeah.
- And you know how to start it, right?
I honestly don't.
I only took like one class.
Ah, Christ.
The engine start button on the right.
Engine start button?
There isn't one.
Yeah, Hummers use keys.
There is a key hole next to the wheel.
Ah!
- [car dings]
- Did you start it?
No, not yet. It isn't working.
What's not working?
- What is wrong with this thing?
- Brakes! Press the brake pedal.
- You weren't stepping on the brakes pedal?
- Guys, really?
You never even told me I had to.
So which one's the brake again?
The left or right one.
It's the one on the left! Come on.
I'm getting my license
when this is over. I swear.
[engine turns over]
All right. What's next?
Shift into D, and hit the gas pedal.
Steer with the wheel. You got that?
I can't hold the phone
and talk to you at the same time.
Give me a minute.
Ah, okay.
- Should I put the seat belt on?
- [Jin-wook] Whatever. Hurry.
- [Young-joo] Put it on.
- Okay.
Why're you so high and mighty
just 'cause you can drive?
It's not even that serious.
I'll be right there.
- [engine revving]
- [yelling] Holy fuck! Shit, man.
- Did I blow the engine?
- Wait, wait.
Hey, take your foot off
the brake, you dumbass.
- [Young-joo sighs]
- Step lightly on the gas.
Fuck. Whoa!
[yelling]
[yelps] Holy fuck!
I almost just died.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[breathing heavily] Oh, shit. I can't.
[yelps] It's going so fast.
It's too fast. [crying]
Please do something. [yells]
You guys gotta help me.
- Don't turn like that.
- Holy shit. How do I steer?
How do I steer? I'm gonna crash. Ah, shit.
- I don't wanna die. Fuck!
- Calm down.
- Fuck! Fuck, fuck!
- Hey, hey. Hey!
Jin-wook. Will you be quiet?
Put your foot on the brake
and push it down lightly, got it?
[zombies snarling]
[panting]
Shit.
[both whimpering]
Private Lee.
What do we do if there's a zombie?
Just please shut your mouth.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
[exhales deeply]
[breathing heavily, whimpers]
[Jae-yoon] Shit.
[both breathing heavily]
Ra In-ho.
Report to command...
that the hotel bathroom is all clear.
There's a more urgent matter.
- [urine trickling]
- [In-ho grunts]
[grunting]
- [snarls]
- [gunshot fires]
- Sir, excuse me.
- [Tae-hwa] Huh?
The food's stored in there.
The rest is over there.
Okay.
- We have no idea how long we'll be here.
- Right.
- Take what's light, and high in calories.
- Hmm.
And don't stop until your packs are full.
- Yes, sir. Right away.
- Right away.
- [Gye-young] Look at this.
- I'll take berries.
[both grunting, gulping]
- Jae-yoon, come back up.
- What?
Look what I brought.
You'll be all right.
You actually got a good one.
Look at you. Brilliant.
[both sucking]
Ah! [sighs]
[Jae-yoon grunts]
- [cell phone vibrates]
- [In-ho gasps]
[water running, swishing]
[Jae-yoon sighs] What?
[In-ho gasps]
- Hey, Private Lee.
- Jesus, what?
We just got Wi-Fi. Wi-Fi!
Wi-Fi.
Oh, my God. Wi-Fi.
Wi-Fi. Young-joo.
YOUNG-JOO, MY LOVE
[ringtone beeping]
- [Young-joo] No, slow down.
- [Jin-wook] Go slow.
[snarling]
VIDEO CHAT... JAE-YOON
- [Young-joo gasps]
- What?
Whoa!
Oh, Young-joo. Hey!
Jae-yoon, hi!
Are you okay? Have you been hurt?
[crying] Everything's okay.
[Young-joo] What about you?
Are you hurt? Are you safe?
I'm okay. I'm not hurt.
Here, just look at me. See?
- Oh, thank God.
- Where are you at?
The A Tower garage, downstairs!
You're still here, right?
- Huh?
- What floor are you on?
I'll come to you.
I'm gonna come get you.
So just tell me which floor you're on.
No, Young-joo.
Why would you do that? You can't.
I had to. I was worried sick.
No, you can't come here, Young-joo.
Uh, what the hell?
Just please tell me what floor you're on.
Young-joo, listen.
This place is really really bad, okay?
You should go to a shelter.
No, I can't. I can't just leave you here.
- No, no. Listen.
- Wait. I'll be right there.
You shouldn't be anywhere
near this place. It's dangerous, okay?
You don't know what I've been through
in the last few days, okay, Jae-yoon?
So, yes, I can.
I'm stronger than you think.
I'll get you out of here.
For the love of God,
just tell me which floor you're on.
[crying]
Oh, Jesus. Young-joo, are you there?
- Uh-huh.
- So, I... I actually...
I don't think I mentioned that
my unit just left A Tower.
So we're not there.
- Huh?
- So you should...
- Go somewhere to hide--
- [In-ho] Suseo.
- Hey.
- There's a Central Command
base camp in Suseo.
First Sergeant was on the phone
talking about it.
- [Young-joo] Jae-yoon.
- Go to Suseo.
- Suseo?
- [Jae-yoon] You'll be safer.
There are soldiers stationed there.
They'll protect you
and we'll meet there, okay?
- Just stay safe and I'll see you in Suseo.
- No.
- You still there? Suseo--
- No, wait.
[gasps] Oh, oh.
Fuck! [crying]
[Jin-wook] Uh... I...
Jae-yoon.
- Oh, shit! I fucked up.
- Uh...
- Sir, may I tell you something?
- Hold on, hold on.
YOUNG-JOO, YOU'RE BREAKING OFF.
Sir, it's a good sign
that she hasn't been hurt.
She made it this far along.
That means she has what it takes
to hold her own out there.
Right?
Yeah, she can survive out there.
We might have a chance.
We'll get out of here and go save her.
Yeah.
- [gunshot fires]
- [both gasp]
- Hey!
- What?
- It's a zombie. [whimpers]
[breathing heavily]
- [Tripeater] What?
- [busy tone beeping]
Why won't it connect?
I need you guys.
Are you there? Come on. [yelps]
Shit, shit! Oh, shit. I'm gonna die!
[yelps] It's too fast. It's way too fast.
I'm gonna crash at this rate.
Ugh! I wanna get out!
Please let me get out! [crying]
- [gunshot fires]
- [zombie snarls]
[Young-man] Holy shit!
Oh, shi--
[Jae-yoon] Hey. It's Sergent Kim.
There he is. Fuck.
[Young-man] Hey.
Are you okay? Sergeant Young-man.
Zombie attack!
- [Kyung-sik exhales]
- Kyung-sik and I killed four.
We're good, don't worry.
Sergeant Kim, you deserve a thumbs up.
There could be more. Keep an eye out.
- [Jae-yoon] Sir.
- They come outta nowhere.
They jump on you.
Aim straight for their head.
[Jae-yoon] Sir.
They ran from there,
when we took 'em out.
- [Kyung-sik] How many did you take down?
- Is that important?
- [zombie snarls]
- [Jae-yoon gasps]
Zombie on your six!
[Young-man yelping]
[whimpers]
- Holy shit!
- [Jae-yoon exclaims]
Let's get a move on.
Jesus.
[Jae-yoon] Wow.
- [Young-man] Did someone fall?
- [In-ho] Let's get out.
[Soo-jeong]
We should take this, and these.
- Grab these bags.
- [Gye-young] This looks good.
Oh, score. Bread.
[Tae-hwa] Stop, stop, stop!
[both] Huh?
Shit! No, wait. Soo-jeong. Wait.
- Stop, Paolo.
- What are you doing?
No soldiers allowed in the back room.
Oh, Paolo.
- Paolo?
- Gye-young, it's you.
- Don't move.
- [Paolo] Sir, wait! Please don't shoot.
Are you all right?
You haven't
been bitten, have you?
- Bitten?
- [Soo-jeong] Yes.
What?
Were you... Were you bitten?
- No, no.
- [Soo-jeong] No?
- No. He's good.
- We still need to check him, all right?
Oh, yeah. Hey, Paolo.
May we check for bites?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Gye-young.
- RIght away.
Paolo.
I don't see any bites.
You alone? Is there anyone else?
There's not. There's no one else.
The lobby upstairs sounded like a war.
So fucking dangerous.
How the hell have you been
sleeping with what's going on?
[Soo-jeong] Huh?
Pills.
- What?
- I don't--
Where did you get that?
You're a chef.
You've been doing drugs here?
No. Melatonin. A sleeping aid.
- So not--
- Look, I'm scared.
I wanna go. You think you guys
can take me to the embassy.
We're not taking you anywhere.
But if you rescue an American,
it's the law, isn't it?
We aren't here to rescue you.
All right, Paolo?
You're kidding me. You're leaving me here?
Jeokbanhajang!
[Jeokbanhajang] The person at fault blames
or scolds someone who has done no wrong.
- You want us to take you? Are you crazy?
- He didn't mean it.
You know what's going on out there?
No, no! Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stay there.
- I think the pills knocked him out.
- I think he really was asleep.
Paolo had no idea.
Paolo. Why, why, why, why?
Just answer the phone.
I need to get out.
[whimpers] Help me.
[zombie snarls]
[whimpers] Shit, shit, shit, shit.
- [grunts]
- [engine revving]
[grunting]
[whimsical music playing]
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey.
It's dangerous! Get out of the way!
Go, go. Move.
Don't jump in front of the car!
[yelling]
- [Jin-wook] Get down.
- [Young-joo shouts]
[brakes screeching]
[Tripeater whimpers]
[pants] Wow.
[both breathing heavily]
Hey!
Whoa. I'm gonna hurl.
Hop in the back. I got this.
- [Jin-wook yelling]
- [tires screeching]
- [Jin-wook] Eat shit!
- [Young-joo shouting]
[Jin-wook cheering]
Die, trash! [grunts]
Jesus!
[yelping]
[Jin-wook] Go to hell,
you sons of bitches.
- [Tripeater] Stop!
- [Young-joo] Stop.
- [Tripeater] Seriously, stop!
- Zombie trash.
I'm dizzy. Stop the car!
Come on, man, what the hell?
[Young-joo yelps]
[loud thudding]
- We're not done yet.
- [Tripeater yelps] Shit!
Crazy asshole!
Please, I can't take it.
[brakes screech]
[all panting]
Isn't it better to be crazier than them?
[Tripeater] Whatever happens,
it's better to be alive.
Stop acting like a maniac.
You think 'cause you found the car,
you're less of a dumbass? Huh?
I guess you forgot that I took you in
when you were dying on the street.
You should remember your place, Tripeater.
Do your parents know
you're walking the streets hammered? Huh?
This is why you repeated
your exams three times.
I feel sorry for your parents.
They're probably disappointed
that you ended up like this.
What are you doing?
You're crazy. Get off of me.
Sounds like you wanna die today.
I'll bite your head off right here.
[Young-joo sighs] Just calm down.
Just take it easy.
You see these eyes?
I wouldn't push your luck.
Uh. All right, all right. I...
Okay, I get it.
You're right, you're right.
Just let go.
[Tripeater sighs]
I might just bite you anyway.
While I appreciate you letting me
tag along with you guys,
just watch who you're talking to.
- [Jin-wook] Mmm-hmm.
- You dick.
All your money's worthless,
when you're an asshole.
Hey, Boozer, don't you agree?
[chuckles]
- Son of a bitch.
- [Tripeater] What? Drive.
[Jin-wook] Mmm-hmm.
- [Paolo] Enjoy.
- [Jae-yoon pants] Thank you so much.
We don't know when
our next meal will be. So eat up.
[all] Yes, sir.
- Split this bread with me.
- [In-ho sighs]
JUNG TAE-HWA 05/04/25
[Paolo] You'll have to pay for this later.
No freebies here.
I hope we all live to see that day.
Sir. Excuse me.
The hotel doesn't allow smoking.
It's prohibited.
You can write a ticket.
- I say you can smoke here.
- My gosh, we're allowed?
- Jae-yoon?
- I got a lighter.
- Mm. Here you go.
- No, no, stop.
No smoking.
This is a Michelin star restaurant.
What the hell?
What are you guys doing here?
- Man. What's your problem?
- Fuck's sake.
You nuts? Are you guys crazy?
Smoking in my fucking restaurant?
- [Kyung-sik] Geez.
- You're smoking, too?
- Chill out.
- You worked here.
Oh, fucking hell.
And you can't vape in here either.
Ugh. Fuck!
- Wait. Where are you going?
- [Paolo] It's ruined.
I'm gonna go grab a soda.
- Sir, I can get it for you.
- It's fine. I can get my own soda.
- [Paolo] I'm gonna die here. Fuck!
- You all right?
Ugh! It's all over.
I'm worried about the future of Korea.
[Soo-jeong] He's still mad.
[metal clanking in distance]
[clanking continues]
[Tae-hwa breathing shakily]
[faint snarling]
[snarling]
- [Tae-hwa yells]
- [gunshot fires]
[all exclaim in surprise]
- [Young-man] Huh?
- What was that?
- A gunshot.
- [In-ho] Get ready.
[Jae-yoon] Go round the table.
Sergeant Kim! Wait. Hold on.
Just wait a minute.
- Lee Jae-yoon
- Please wait.
It's Sergeant Young-man!
Are you alright, sir?
Shit...
[zombie snarling in distance]
I'm gonna come in there.
I just need you to--
[all whimpering]
- [all yelping]
- Jesus Christ.
[snarls]
[all] Huh?
[all exclaiming]
[hissing]
[Jae-yoon] Holy fuck.
[all yelping]
- [Soo-jeong whimpers]
- [Gye-young] Get it, get it.
[all whimpering]
[zombie grunts]
[breathing shakily]
[Jae-yoon whimpers]
[all sighing in relief]
[Jae-yoon] Oh, shit.
[faint snarling]
[all gasping]
- First Sergeant.
- [Jae-yoon] What?
[all breathing shakily]
Jesus.
[snarling continues]
His nose. The closer
to the brain the wound is,
the faster it spreads.
[hissing]
[all whimpering]
[tense music playing]
[Young-man breathing shakily]
[sobbing]
[Jae-yoon] Shoot, shoot, shoot!
[tense music fades out]
I have to get to
Seoul Hospital before Suseo.
- So first we'll stop there.
- A hospital?
My mom's in there.
Ah! I'm sorry. Is she sick?
I never told you, did I?
The hospital is hers.
She bought the place a while ago.
I need to get to Suseo, okay?
That's where Jae-yoon said--
Are we supposed to just
let this kid wither away?
[Young-joo] Huh?
We'll get him treatment
as soon as we get to the hospital.
And you should also get looked at.
Suseo station's right down the street.
Once we're done, we'll go.
- But you need to get treated there, okay?
- Okay.
[clears throat]
[retches]
Hey! Do that out the window, dude.
Stop the car. I need to go.
Are you stupid? We can't stop here.
If you don't stop, maybe I'll--
Ah! No, no, no, no. All right, all right.
- [brakes screech]
- [Jin-wook] Jesus Christ.
Shit. This kid is insane.
[Young-joo] Hey!
[Tripeater grunting]
[retches]
Oh! Is there a bathroom here
you could use?
I had to puke.
You could just do that
like wherever you want.
Ew. So gross. That's just you, man.
[Tripeater chuckles]
[sighs] Black pepper ramen
would change the game right now.
Hey, if you don't know yet,
it's amazing at carrying a hangover.
I know it's crazy.
- Oh, I see you there.
- Ha!
Yeah, those drinks are really strong.
I'm sober now, at least.
Yeah, it's kind of wearing off
for me, too.
- I think that I'll head back now.
- Huh?
[sighs] No, let's stay together
and get you to the hospital.
- Then we'll go to Suseo.
- No, don't worry.
I'm scared of hospitals. I'll stay.
I go back home and study.
What, for school? What a dumbass.
I just think the zombie
the situation could end any day.
It's a good idea to be ready.
I can take care of myself now.
- [zombies snarling]
- [Young-joo gasps]
Leave me here.
Get out while you can.
- I can handle this.
- Yeah. See ya.
We're going to the hospital.
Hey, you know you don't
have to do this, right.
Ah, like I always say, "No worry."
No worry?
[Jin-wook] No worry. He wants to stay.
Why don't you hit
the books, like you said?
That'd be better.
[Tripeater grunts]
Okay.
[grunting]
Hey, just go. Drive away, you moron.
- Hey, wanna repeat that?
- Just step on it right now...
moron.
Hold on. What?
Wait. Jin-wook.
Hey.
Be careful.
- Are you gonna be okay?
- [engine whirring]
[zombies snarling]
Wait. Oh, shit. Wait. [grunts]
Don't go. [grunting]
[snarling continues]
[yelling]
[grunting]
Do you think that he's all right?
[sentimental music playing]
[Young-joo exhales]
Hold on. Did we ever get his real name?
[sighs]
I should've asked
what his name was.
He was transforming already.
If he came with us, we'd be dead tomorrow.
Now we go our own ways.
[sentimental music continues]
No worry.
Dumbass.
Now we go our own ways.
No worry.
[grunts] Shit, man. Come here. Go on.
Die! Die!
[grunts] Die!
Fuck you!
Die. [grunting]
How's that feel?
That's easier than studying for me.
[grunting]
[groaning]
[music stops]
[tense music plays]
[snarls]
[male choir vocalizing]
[man singing Korean song]
[man continues singing Korean song]
[song fades out]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[music fades out]